sosvox.org 2018-12-26

# Privacy Policies

The following **Privacy Policies** apply to the entire content of the **SOSVOX.ORG** domain.  

## 1- Declaration of Good Practices

**SOSVOX.ORG** respects your privacy and is committed to protecting the personal information you provide while using the Website.

**SOSVOX.ORG** is committed to complying with current legislation on the protection of personal data: **REGULATION (EU) 2016/679 OF THE EUROPEAN PARLIAMENT AND OF THE COUNCIL of 27 April 2016** (hereinafter, RGPD), and by Law 34/2002, of 11 July, on Information Society Services and Electronic Commerce (LSSI-CE).

**SOSVOX.ORG** will request, prior to providing your personal data, that you tick the appropriate box to read and accept this Privacy Policy.

We will not collect any personal information from you unless you voluntarily provide it to us with your free, express and unambiguous consent.  

## 2- Responsible for the Processing of Your Personal Data

Company Name: Aurat S.A.  
R.U.T. Number: 217646060012  
Head Office Address: Constituyente 1467 - Piso 20 - CP 11200. Montevideo (O.R. Uruguay)  
E-mail data protection: dpo@sosvox.org  

## 3- Data Protection Officer (DPO) of SOSVOX.ORG

For further information, or for any other questions regarding this Privacy Policy in relation to the processing of your data, please do not hesitate to contact our Data Protection Officer (DPO) at the following e-mail address: dpo@sosvox.org  

## 4- Purpose of the use of Your Data

**SOSVOX.ORG** may use your information for the purpose of providing you with Technical Support, Customer Service, Sending Notifications, Newsletters and/or Promotional Announcements and Account Maintenance in general.

In addition, we inform you that in these referenced treatments we do not carry out exclusively automated decisions that may affect you in any way, nor are there any subsequent purposes for which your data may be used.  

## 5- What is the origin of your data?

As a general rule, the data processed by **SOSVOX.ORG** are provided by the data subject him/herself through the various forms on the website, with free, express and unequivocal consent.  

## 6- Period of storage of your data

The personal data provided will be kept for the period of time strictly necessary to carry out the purposes described above and in any case for the period of time determined on the basis of the following criteria:

a) Compliance with legal obligations under the law of the Union and/or Member States.  
b) Attention to your requests and requests.  
c) Prescription of legal liabilities that may arise from the relationship established with you.  
d) Request for deletion of data by you in the appropriate cases.  

## 7- Information about Your Rights

Under the terms and to the extent set out in current legislation, any person is entitled to:

  * Access to your Personal Data and to the information related to its treatment.
  * Request rectification of inaccurate data.
  * To request the deletion of data when, among other reasons, they are no longer **SOSVOX.ORG** will no longer process the data except for the purpose for which they were collected, in which case **SOSVOX.ORG** will no longer process the data except for the purpose of exercising or defending any claims.
  * Request a restriction on the processing of your data, in which case they may be processed only with your consent, with the exception of their retention and use for the exercise or defence of claims or for the protection of the rights of another natural or legal person or on grounds of important public interest of the European Union or of a particular Member State.
  * To oppose the processing of your data, in which case **SOSVOX.ORG** will stop processing the data, except for the defence of possible claims.
  * Receive in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format the personal data that you have provided to **SOSVOX.ORG** , or request **SOSVOX.ORG** to forward it directly to another party where technically possible.
  * Withdraw the consent granted to carry out the purposes previously informed through the corresponding web forms and included in the present Privacy Policy, without affecting the legality of the treatment based on the consent prior to its withdrawal.

These rights may be exercised directly by the data subject or by legal or voluntary representative, by sending an express request, together with a copy of your National Identity Card or equivalent proving your identity, to the e-mail address dpo@sosvox.org. Likewise, you may submit a complaint to the Spanish Data Protection Agency, especially when you consider that you have not obtained satisfaction in the exercise of your rights, through the website set up for this purpose by the corresponding Control Authority.  

## 8- Recipients of your Personal Data

By using **SOSVOX.ORG** , you agree that we may transfer your personal information in connection with the purposes set forth in this Privacy Policy.  
In some cases, some of our sponsors and related services may be provided by distribution partners (Third Parties). You understand and agree that each distributor will collect and use your personal information in accordance with its own privacy policies (which you will have access to when you register on such Websites).

When you have provided us with personal information for a particular purpose, we may disclose your information to other companies that we have contracted with to assist us in fulfilling your request. This may include, but is not limited to, suppliers, collaborators, strategic partners.

We may also disclose your personal information to law enforcement in connection with criminal investigations, fraud investigations, intellectual property infringement, or other suspicious illegal activities, or when we deem it necessary, in our sole discretion, to protect **SOSVOX.ORG's** legitimate interests.

Sometimes we share general, demographic or aggregate (non-personal) information with third parties about our user base, but that information does not include any personal information.  

### Classification of Information.

#### **a). About Personal Information**

**SOSVOX.ORG** does not collect any personal information unless you provide it to us voluntarily. Only personal information necessary to meet your demands and our legitimate business objectives will be requested.

From time to time, you may be asked to provide additional personal information, such as your mailing address, telephone number, etc. In each case, no new personal information will be collected without your free, express and unambiguous consent.

When using any of the Site's communication functions, your IP (Internet Protocol) address may be stored in our records.

In some jurisdictions, IP addresses may be legally viewed as personally identifiable information.

#### **b). About Non-Personal Information**

When you log in to **SOSVOX.ORG** , system specifications (such as operating system, web browser, Java version, RAM memory, video card, monitor, system configuration, etc.) may be reviewed/recorded by us to analyze and optimize your experience in order to provide you with better service.

**SOSVOX.ORG** may collect, among other things, information about the type of Internet browser and/or operating system of the computer you are using, the domain name of your Internet service provider. To this end, **SOSVOX.ORG** may use cookies and other technologies.

Your visits to our Website, and the information provided through these technologies, will be anonymous unless you provide us with personal information or have provided such information in the past.  

## 9- International Data Transfers

In the processing of your data, there are international transfers of your data to countries outside the Member States of the European Union. **SOSVOX.ORG** has retained the services of technology providers located, for example, in the USA who have adequate safeguards and guarantees to preserve your privacy under the Privacy Shield Agreement, ensuring an adequate level of protection of personal data.  

## 10- Security Measures

The personal data of our users are stored in a database owned by AURAT S.A., which guarantees the appropriate technical and structural measures to preserve the integrity and security of the personal information provided, although it is not responsible for them or for any damages caused, including negligence of our operators, in which case the possible vulnerability or violation will be notified to the competent authorities.

No website or Internet transmission is completely secure. Consequently, **SOSVOX.ORG** cannot guarantee that unauthorized access, loss of data due to hacking, or other breaches will never occur. Use of **SOSVOX.ORG** is at your own risk and responsibility.

**SOSVOX.ORG** urges you to take steps to keep your personal information secure by memorizing your password or keeping it in a secure place (separate from your account information) or by generating backup copies of your content.  

## 11- Modification of the Privacy Policy

**SOSVOX.ORG** reserves the right to modify its Privacy Policy, according to its own criteria, or motivated by a doctrinal change of the European Data Protection Committee (EDC) or of the national supervisory authority (Spanish Data Protection Agency), legislative or jurisprudential. Any changes to the Privacy Policy will be communicated by other means, such as sending corporate emails to users and posting a notice on our home page.
